Guide to the CASA Latina Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- ORGANIZATION SUBJECT FILES [SERIE 9: ARCHIVOS POR TEMA DE ORGANIZACIONES], 1993-2009; SERIES 9 (Box-folder 1/17, 1/19, 1/20, 1/22-24, 1/26, 1/37-38, 1/45-47, 1/50-58, 1/69-90, 2/1, 2/2, 2/6, 2/8-11, 2/14-15, 2/27, 2/29-32, 2/39, 2/63-67, 2/75, 3/37-38, 4/41, 4/46, 5/1, 5/7, 5/10, 5/12, 5/15-16, 5/
  - Edmonds Unitarian Universalist Church [Iglesia Unitaria Universalista Edmonds], 2007 (Box-folder 11/34)
  - Employees Community Fund of Boeing [Fondo Comunitario de Empleos de Boeing], 2001 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Environment Works (Department of Neighborhoods) [Trabajos de Ambiente (Departamento de Barrios)], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/52)
  - Fax of Npower Seattle [Fax de NPower Seattle], 2005 (Box-folder 1/89)
  - Feasibility Study--Paul G.Allen Foundation [Estudio de Factibilidad-- Fundación Paul G. Allen], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Fedex Service of Corporate Social Responsibility [Servicio de Responsabilidad Social Corporativa Fedex], 2005 (Box-folder 1/54)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation Conference [Conferencia de Compañerismo de Reconciliación], 1997 (Box-folder 7/53)
  - Foster Foundation [Fundación Foster], 2006-2008 (Box-folder 11/32)
  - Freidbery Family Foundation [Fundación Familia Freidbery], 2001 (Box-folder 1/56)
  - Funding Exchange [Intercambio de Fondos], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/57)
  - Henry M. Jackson Foundation [Fundación Henry M. Jackson], 2006 (Box-folder 11/33)
  - Homeless and Housing Services RFP Process [Proceso RFP para Viviendas y Servicios a Personas Sin Hogar], 1997 (Box-folder 5/49)
  - Human Services Budget Changes [Cambios al Propuesto de Servicios Humanos], 2005 (Box-folder 1/38)
  - IBM Corporation [Corporación IBM], 1996 (Box-folder 5/54)
  - Jeffris Wood Foundation (Women's Program) [Fundación Jeffris Wood (Programa de Mujeres)], 2003 (Box-folder 1/69)
  - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation [Fundación Jessie Smith Noyes], 2006 (Box-folder 11/31)
  - Jewish Fund for Justice (Declined) [Fondo Judío para Justicia (Rechazado)], 2001 (Box-folder 1/70)
  - Jewish Fund for Justice [Fondo Judío por la Justicia], 1996 (Box-folder 5/52)
  - Jewish Women's Funding Network [La Red de Financiación de Mujeres Judías], 2007-2009 (Box-folder 11/30)
  - June & Julian Foss Foundation [Fundación June & Julian Foss], 2004 (Box-folder 1/55)
  - Kawabe Foundation (Bank of America) [Fundación Kawabe (Bank of America)], 2004 (Box-folder 1/72)
  - King county Children & family commission [Condado King Comisión para Niñxs y Familias], 2000-2004 (Box-folder 1/71)
  - King County DOT: Job Access and Reverse Commute [King County DOT: Acceso al Trabajo y Viaje Inverso], 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - King County Public Health--Para Los Ninos Program [Salud Pública Condado King--Programa For the Kids], 2006 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Kirkpatrick Family Foundation [Fundación Kirkpatrick Family], 2005 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Knossos Foundation [Fundación Knossos], 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5/41)
  - Knossos Foundation [Fundación Knossos], 2000-2005 (Box-folder 1/75)
  - Kongsgaard Goldman, 1999 (Box-folder 5/31)
  - Kongsgaard--Goldman [Fundación Kongsgaard--Goldman], 2000 (Box-folder 1/73)
  - Laubach Literacy International [Laubach Organización por Literacia Internacional], 1995-1996 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Lauchach Literacy Action (Women in USA) [Acción por Literacia Lauchach (Mujeres en EE.UU.)], 1997-2002 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Lincoln towing [Remolque Towing], 2003 (Box-folder 1/74)
  - Literacy Americorps, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Marguerite Casey Foundation (1 of 2) [Fundación Marguerite Casey (1 de 2)], 2003-2004 September (Box-folder 1/76)
  - Marguerite Casey Foundation (2 of 2) [Fundación Marguerite Casey (2 de 2)], 2003-2004 September (Box-folder 1/77)
  - Marguerite Casey Foundation [Fundación Marguerite Casey], 2004-2006 (Box-folder 11/27)
  - Marguerite Casey Foundation [Fundación Marguerite Casey], 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/28)
  - Massena Foundation (Community Relation/Belltown Community) [Fundación Massena (Relaciones Comunitarias/Comunidad Belltown)], 2002 (Box-folder 1/81)
  - Massena Foundation [Fundación Massena], 2006 (Box-folder 11/29)
  - Medina Foundation [Fundación Medina], 2005-2007 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Medina Foundation [Fundación Medina], 2005 (Box-folder 1/82)
  - Medtronic Foundation [Fundación Medtronic], 2006 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Metro Bus Ticket Program (1 of 2) [Programa de Boletos para Autobús Metro (1 de 2)], 2000-2003 (Box-folder 1/83)
  - Metro Bus Ticket Program (2 of 2) [Programa de Boletos para Autobús Metro (2 de 2)], 2004-2008 (Box-folder 1/84)
  - Metro Bus Tickets [Boletos de Autobús Metro], 2007 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Metro Human Services Fund [Fondo para Servicios Humanos Metro], 1996 (Box-folder 5/47)
  - Metrocenter YMCA Adult Education for Homeless [Metrocenter YMCA Educación para Adultos Sin Hogar], 1993-1994 (Box-folder 5/24)
  - Millionaire Club Charity Inc. [Club de Caridad de Millonarios], 1993-1994 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Muckleshoot Charitable Fund [Fondo Caritativo Muckleshoot], 2006 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Muckleshoot Charity Fund [Fondo Caritative Muckleshoot], 2005 (Box-folder 1/79)
  - Neighborhood Matching Fund (1 of 4) [Fondo Correspondiente del Barrio (1 de 4)], 1999 (Box-folder 5/26)
  - Neighborhood Matching Fund (2 of 4) [Fondo Correspondiente del Barrio (2 de 4)], 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Neighborhood Matching Fund (3 of 4) [Fondo Correspondiente del Barrio (3 de 4)], 1999 (Box-folder 5/28)
  - Neighborhood Matching Fund (4 of 4) [Fondo Correspondiente del Barrio (4 de 4)], 1999 (Box-folder 5/29)
  - Nesholm Family Foundation [Fundación Nesholm Family], 2008 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - New Citizen Initiative Core Services [Servicios Básicos para Nuevos Ciudadanos], 1997 (Box-folder 5/45)
  - New Voices National Fellowship Program [Programa Nacional de Beca Universitaria Nuevas Voces], 2006 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Nonprofit Assistance Center [Centro de Asistencia para Organizaciones sin Fines de Lucro], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1/85)
  - Nonprofit Assistance Center, PLNDH [Centro de Asistencia para Organizaciones sin Fines de Lucro], 2004 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Norcliffe Foundation [Fundación Norcliffe], 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Northwest Institute for Families Report [Informe de Instituto Noroeste sobre Familias], 1997 (Box-folder 8/50)
  - NPower Seattle [NPower Seattle], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/88)
  - Office of Adult Literacy Allocations [Repartos de la Oficina para Literacia Adulta], 1997-1998 (Box-folder 8/51)
  - OneFamily Foundation [Fundación OneFamily], 2004-2007 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Oregon Community Foundation [Fundación Comunitarie Oregon], 2005 (Box-folder 1/90)
  - Pac 10 Objectives for 2004 [Objetivos Pac 10 para 2004] (Box-folder 3/38)
  - Peace Development Fund [Fondo para Desarrollar Paz], 1999 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - People of Color Against Aids Networking [Redes de Gente de Color Contra SIDA], 2001 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Plymouth Congregational Church [Iglesia Congregacional Plymouth], 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Premiere Conferencing [Conferencias Premiere], 2005 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Project Lift-Off (Department of Neighborhoods) [Proyecto Despegue (Departamento de Barrios)], 2004 (Box-folder 1/53)
  - Public Welfare Fund [Fondo Bienestar Público], 2007-2008 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Race Relation & Social Justice (Department of Neighborhoods) [Relaciones Raciales y Justicia Social (Departamento de Barrios)], 2003 (Box-folder 1/47)
  - Refugee Women's Alliance (ReWA) [Alianza para Mujeres Refugiadas (ReWA)], 2006 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Satterbery Foundation [Fundación Satterbery], 1999 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - Seattle Foundation, PLNDH [Fundación Seattle, PLNDH], 2005 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Seattle Partners for Healthy Families [Socios de Seattle para Familias Saludables], 2000 (Box-folder 2/27)
  - Seattle People Fund, PLNDH [Fondos para Personas Seattle, PLNDH ], 2005 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Seattle Public Schools [Escuelas Públicas de Seattle], 2008 (Box-folder 9/55)
  - Seattle Symphony [Sinfonía de Seattle], 1996-1997 (Box-folder 5/48)
  - SEIU Local 6, 1996 (Box-folder 8/37)
  - SEIU Local 775, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 8/38)
  - SOAR Education Fund: Children's Education & Women's Group [Fondo de Educación SOAR: Educación para Niñxs y Grupo de Mujeres], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - SOAR Matching, PLNDH [SOAR Matching, PLNDH], 2006 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Social Justice Fund [Fondo Justicia Social], 2006 (Box-folder 2/29)
  - Social Justice Fund [Fondo Justicia Social], 2007 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Social Justice Fund Northwest [Fondo para Justicia Social del Noroeste], 2003-2005 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Sociological Initiatives Foundation [Fundación Iniciativas Sociológicas], 2003 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - Starbucks Foundation [Fundación Starbucks], 1997-1999 (Box-folder 5/40)
  - Taqueria Latinos, 2003 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - The Barbara Bush Foundation for Family Literacy [Fundación para Literacia Familiar Barbara Bush], 1995-1996 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - The Foster Foundation [Fundación Foster], 2004-2006 (Box-folder 1/58)
  - The Foster Foundation [Fundación Foster], 1997-2008 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - The Seattle Times Program [Programa Seattle Times], 1996-1999 (Box-folder 5/19)
  - The Starbucks Foundation Family Literacy Program [Programa para Literacidad Familiar de Fundación Starbucks], 2003 (Box-folder 2/31)
  - The Stooker Foundation [Fundación Stooker], 2005 (Box-folder 2/32)
  - U.S.-Belgium Cultural Crossing [Cruce Cultural de EE.UU. y Bélgica], 2007-2009 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - United Way Endowment Fund [United Way Fondo de Dotación], 1997 (Box-folder 5/43)
  - United Way Pilot Cause Area Funding [Fondo Causa Piloto United Way], 1997 (Box-folder 5/46)
  - United Way Venture Funds [United Way Fondo de Riesgo], 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5/33)
  - UW Work Study Job Description [Descripción de Programa de Estudio y Trabajo UW ], 2006 (Box-folder 2/63)
  - UW Worker Safe Study [Estudio de Trabajador Segure UW], 2006 (Box-folder 2/64)
  - Venture Funds, PLNDH [Fondos Venture, PLNDH], 2006 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Washington Women's Foundation [Fundación de Mujeres en Washington], 2004 (Box-folder 2/67)
  - Washington Women's Foundation [Fundación Mujeres de Washington], 2006-2008 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Western States Center [Centro Western States], 2007 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Wood Family Foundation [Fundación Familia Wood], 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - Workers' Alliance for a Just Economy (WAJE) [Alianza de Trabajadores por Una Economía Justa (WAJE)], 2008 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - World Vision [Visión Mundial], 2002-2004 (Box-folder 2/75)
- CASA LATINA WEBSITE [SERIE 10: SITIO WEB DE CASA LATINA], approximately 2013-2020; SERIES 10 (Electronic file Website)
  Captures of the CASA Latina website crawled by the UW Libraries Archive-It instance beginning in 2013. These routine crawls are ongoing.